A message in a bottle sent out to sea by a New Hampshire man more than five decades
ago was found 1,500 miles away.
And has been returned to his daughter.
The long lost message was discovered by Clint Buffington of Utah while he was
vacationing. And has been returned to his daughter.
vacationing. Buffington says he found a soda bottle half buried in the sand that
looked like it had been there since the beginning of time.
Buffington says he found a soda bottle half buried in the sand that looked like it
had been there since the beginning of time.
The note inside the bottle said,
Return to 419 Ocean Street and receive a reward of $150 from Richard and Tina
Pearce, owners of the Beachcomber Motel.
The note inside the bottle said,
Return to 419 Ocean Street and receive a reward of $150 from Richard and Tina
Pearce, owners of the Beachcomber Motel.
The note inside the bottle said,
to 419 Ocean Street and receive a reward of $150 from Richard and Tina Pearce,
owners of the Beachcomber Motel.
The motel was owned by the parents of Paula Pearce in 1960.
Her father had written the note as a joke and had thrown it into the Atlantic Ocean.
Her father had written